<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<LanguageData>
  <LetterLabelManhunterPackArrived>Infected pack</LetterLabelManhunterPackArrived>

  <!-- Self-tame -->
  <LetterLabelAnimalSelfTame>{1_kind} wants safety</LetterLabelAnimalSelfTame>
  <LetterAnimalSelfTame>{0} has recognised this community as safe from the infected and has decided to stay with you.</LetterAnimalSelfTame>
  <LetterAnimalSelfTameAndNameNumerical>{0} has recognised this community as safe from the infected and has decided to stay with you. It is now designated {ANIMAL_nameFull}.</LetterAnimalSelfTameAndNameNumerical>
  <LetterAnimalSelfTameAndName>{0} has recognised this community as safe from the infected and has decided to stay with you. Colonists have decided to name it {ANIMAL_nameFull}.</LetterAnimalSelfTameAndName>

  <!-- Farm animals wander in -->
  <LetterLabelFarmAnimalsWanderIn>{0} want shelter</LetterLabelFarmAnimalsWanderIn>
  <LetterFarmAnimalsWanderIn>A group of {0}, abandoned or lost, have wandered into the area.\n\nThey seem accustomed to human contact and seem to recognise this place as a haven
    from infected attacks.\n\nThey have decided they are joining the colony.</LetterFarmAnimalsWanderIn>

  <!-- Trader caravan -->
  <LetterTraderCaravanArrival>A caravan from {0} is approaching. They are a {1} and appear to want to camp in relative safety for a while.</LetterTraderCaravanArrival>
  <LetterCaravanArrivalCommonWarning>They wish to stay near the colony while they prepare to face the infected once more. They will hang around for some time before leaving. You can attack them - but this will anger their faction!</LetterCaravanArrivalCommonWarning>

  <!-- Journey-related -->
  <EscapeShipFoundLabel>Ship found</EscapeShipFoundLabel>
  <EscapeShipFound>You've reached the coordinates sent by (*Name)Charlon Whitestone(/Name) and discovered the hidden starship.\n\nThe ship's reactor is still in deep hibernation mode, so it can't fly yet. You can start it up by interacting with the computer core.\n\n(*Name)Charlon Whitestone(/Name) warns you that the startup process will take about 15 days, and the energy signature will be detectable from a long distance away. This sort of energy signature indicates interstellar flight capability, and will attract those desperate to escape the infected hordes. Unfortunately the frequency of the signal irritates the infected and they will also come to stop the noise at any cost.\n\nYou will be assaulted with an intensity you've never seen. Make sure your defenses are prepared first.</EscapeShipFound>

  <!-- Caravan meeting -->
  <CaravanMeetingTitle>Caravan meeting by {0}</CaravanMeetingTitle>
  <CaravanMeeting>{0} has met peacefully with a caravan from {1}. They do not appear to be infected but you can never be sure they aren't still incubating. The other caravan is composed of:\n\n{2}</CaravanMeeting>
</LanguageData>
